Ethnic Heritage and Language Schools in America Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 17: General Casimir Pulaski Polish School, Chicago, Illinois (Fieldworker Margy McClain)
  - Manuscripts
    - Curriculum materials, D.1. through D.3. (Box 16)
    - Curriculum materials, E.1. through E.9. (Box 17)
    - Curriculum materials, F.1. through F.5.d. (Box 17)
    - Curriculum materials, F.6.a. through F.6.c. (Box 17)
    - 3 publications in Polish (Box 17)
    - Curriculum materials-1) G.1. (Box 18)
    - Polish – Appendices (Box 18)
    - Polish – Final reports (Box 18)
    - Microfilmed material (Reel 7)
  - Sound Recordings
    - Interviews, April 30-June 2, 1982, 10 sound cassettes and 24 7-inch reels; AFS 23,649-AFS 23,683
  - Graphic Images
    - Slides, May 8-28, 1982, 100 slides
    - Black and white negatives, May 1-28, 1982, 11 rolls
    - Enlargements, 2 black and white prints (8 x 10 inch) (Box 13)
- Series 18: Polish Curriculum Materials by Ewa Hauser
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 18)
    - Photo inventory and corresponding contact sheets (Box 18)
    - Final report (Box 18)
- Series 19: The Official Portuguese School of the Taunton Sports Club, Taunton, Massachusetts (Fieldworker Marsha Penti)
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 18)
    - Slide and photo logs and corresponding contact sheets (Box 18)
    - 13 publications in Portuguese (Box 19)
    - 4 publications in Portuguese (Box 20)
    - Curriculum materials (Box 20)
    - Curriculum, supplementary materials (Box 20)
    - Publications, news clippings, etc. (Box 20)
    - Final reports (Box 20)
    - Microfilmed material (Reel 7)
  - Sound Recordings
    - Interviews, April 21-June 9, 1982, 16 sound cassettes; AFS 23,684-AFS 23,700
  - Graphic Images
    - Slides, June 25, 1982, 37 slides
    - Black and white negatives, April 14-June 25, 1982, 17 rolls
    - Enlargements, 6 black and white prints (8 x 10 inch) (Box 18)
- Series 20: The Atatürk School [Turkish], New York, New York (Fieldworker Maurie Sacks)
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 20)
    - Slide and photo logs and corresponding contact sheets (Box 20)
    - Curriculum materials – 2) A and B through 3) A (Box 21)
    - Publications, news clippings, etc. - 1) A through 1) I (Box 21)
    - Final reports (Box 21)
    - Microfilmed material (Reel 8)
  - Sound Recordings
    - Interviews, May 1-22, 1982, 9 sound cassettes; AFS 23,701-AFS 23,705
  - Graphic Images
  - Black and white negatives, May 8-29, 1982, 13 rolls
    - Enlargements, 4 black and white prints (8 x 10 inch) (Box 20)
- Series 21: St. Michael's Ukrainian Orthodox Church, Woonsocket, Rhode Island (Fieldworkers Carol O. Bell and Mary Louise Haas)
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 21)
    - Slide and photo logs and corresponding contact sheets (Box 21)
    - Curriculum materials (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Final reports (Box 21)
    - Microfilmed material (Reel 8)
  - Sound Recordings
    - Interviews, April 30-May 30, 1982, 13 sound cassettes; AFS 23,706-AFS 23,718
  - Graphic Images
    - Slides, April 30-May 30, 1982, 20 slides
    - Black and white negatives, April 30-May 30, 1982, 6 rolls
    - Enlargements, 1 black and white print (8 x 10 inch) (Box 21)
- Series 22: East Harlem Music School [Urban Caribbean/Hispanic], New York, New York (Fieldworker Morton Marks)
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 22)
    - Slide and photo logs and corresponding contact sheets (Box 22)
    - Final report (Box 22)
    - Microfilmed material (Reel 8)
  - Sound Recordings
    - Interviews, May 25-August 7, 1982, 6 sound cassettes and 7 7-inch reels; AFS 23,388-AFS 23,400
  - Graphic Images
    - Slides, May 30-August 7, 1982, 67 slides
    - Black and white negatives, May 20-June 2, 1982, 3 rolls
    - Enlargements, 2 black and white prints (8 x 10 inch) (Box 22)
- Series 23: Ethiopian School, Washington, D.C. (Fieldworker Elena Bradunas)
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 22)
    - Curriculum materials (Box 22)
    - Microfilmed material (Reel 8)
  - Graphic Images
    - Black and white negatives, undated, 18 rolls
    - Contact sheets (Box 22)
    - Enlargements, 6 black and white prints (8 x 10 inch) (Box 22)
- Series 24: K. Donelaitis Lithuanian School, Rockville, Maryland (Fieldworker Elena Bradunas)
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 22)
    - Microfilmed material (Reel 8)
  - Graphic Images
    - Black and white negatives, undated, 7 rolls
    - Contact sheets (Box 22)
    - Enlargements, 1 black and white print (8 x 10 inch) (Box 22)
- Series 25: End Products
  - Correspondence, newsletters, workshops (Box 29)
- Series 26: General Ethnic Related Materials
  - Manuscripts
    - Contents (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1940 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1956 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1969 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1976 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1978 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1980 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1981 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1982 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1983 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Articles, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Articles, Undated (Box 29)
- Series 27: Ethnic Specific Materials
  - Manuscripts
    - Articles (arranged by ethnic group) (Box 30)
Manuscripts and Microfilm Inventory
See PDF for more detailed inventory of manuscripts and materials copied to microfilm, which includes correspondence, fieldnotes, sound recording logs, titles of curriculum materials and names of interviewees.